whotrades.com 2015-06-02

# Privacy Policy

WhoTrades Ltd (Seychelles) committed to treating personal information we obtain through our web site with respect for your privacy concerns, and in accordance with the Privacy Policy set forth below. The following Privacy Policy describes WhoTrades Ltd’s policies concerning the use of personal information of all users collected via this web site.

## Purpose of this Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how WhoTrades Ltd treats the personally identifiable information that is collected about you when you visit the www.whotrades.com web site. This policy also describes our treatment of personally identifiable information about you that our business partners may share with us.

## What is personally Identifiable Information

"Personally identifiable information" is information that we can use to identify you as an individual. Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, telephone number, Social Security number, date of birth and any other information that is connected with your identity.

## Information This Privacy Policy Does Not Apply to

This privacy policy does not apply to information collected about you by anyone except WhoTrades Ltd. Any information you provide when you visit web sites other than www.whotrades.com or when you purchase any products or services that may be offered or advertised on www.whotrades.com by companies other than WhoTrades Ltd is subject to the privacy policies of the third party organizations that run and/or own these web sites.

## Information from Third Party Sources

WhoTrades Ltd may on occasion combine information we receive online with information we have obtained through third party sources to enhance our ability to market those products or services that may be of interest to you.

## Web Site Usage Information

WhoTrades Ltd automatically collects IP addresses and web site usage information from you when you visit the www.whotrades.com web site. This information helps us evaluate how our users navigate and use our web site.

## Use of Information

WhoTrades Ltd uses personally identifiable information collected from you for the following general purposes:

  * to fulfill your requests for specific products and services; 
  * to improve the design and content of our site;
  * to contact you about special offers, products or services that may be of interest to you;
  * to provide you with customer service.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

WhoTrades Ltd may share or disclose personally identifiable information about you to other companies or individuals when:

  * we have your consent to share the information;
  * we utilize third party service providers to provide products, services or functions on our behalf and require these service providers to agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information;
  * we have entered into a business relationship with a third party company or an individual whom we believe and expect will conform with our Privacy Policy;
  * we need to protect our legal rights (for example, if we are trying to collect money you owe us or we are trying to enforce our agreements with you);
  * we must comply with applicable laws to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities.

Aggregate information is information that we (or third party service providers on our behalf) collect about WhoTrades Ltd web site users on an anonymous basis. We may share aggregate demographic and usage information with our prospective and actual business partners, advertisers and other third parties.

## Cookies

"Cookies" are small amounts of data that a Web site can send to your web browser and store on your computer. Cookies are created at a web server, sent back to the browser and requested to be stored by the browser. If the browser agrees to store them, the browser will send them back to the web server each time a request is sent to the web server. Cookies can be regularly deleted or disabled. However, this may affect the interaction with the web server, and you may be required to login again and you may not be able to use the web site. Cookies do not contain personal information about you (unless you knowingly provide it). Cookies can note that your browser was used to visit certain sites, pages, or advertisements on a certain date. WhoTrades Ltd does not store sensitive or private information in any cookie which is sent to your browser.

You do have control over cookies. Most browsers can be set to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. You can set most browsers to refuse to accept cookies, although this may affect your internet experience. You can also erase cookies that are already on your computer. For more information on working with cookies, consult the user manual, FAQ, or "Help" function of your specific browser.

We use third−party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## Security

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that meet or exceed industry standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. We protect your account information by placing it on the secure portion of our Web site, using firewalls and other security technology to protect our network and systems from external attacks, and requiring you to enter a unique user name and password to access your account information online. Also, we utilize SSL to protect the privacy of the information which is communicated between your computer and our servers. You can always verify the identity of our web site because we use web server certificates which are signed by a trusted third party. Our employees (for example, customer service and compliance personnel) and third party service providers have access to your nonpublic personal information only on a "need to know" basis. We conduct regular internal audits of our business practices and procedures, examining confidentiality standards and information access in order to protect your personal information. In addition to our security measures, you can also take steps to maximize your security online and to protect your confidential information. First and foremost, don't choose a trivial password and don't post it on your computer. Don't use a public computer unless you can verify that it's not capturing key strokes and that you can erase all of your information from it once you've finished.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

WhoTrades Ltd may change this policy from time to time without notice. Any changes to this policy will be promptly posted on this web site so we encourage you to refer back to this policy each time that you visit. Your use of WhoTrades Ltd 's web site after any changes have been posted will constitute your agreement to the modified Privacy Policy.
